Gabriel Branco da Silva

3 and a half years of experience with IT infrastructures, bare-metal servers, hardware... 2 years modeling and developing software in Go, main experience with APIs, knows Docker, Kubernetes, GCP VMs and routes, ec2 instances and route 53, gitlab ci/cd, postgres cli and a few other things.

23 years old Votuporanga-SP - Brazil linkedin.com/in/igab-dev github.com/igab-dev +55 17 99205-3636 gbrancods@gmail.com

EXPERIENCE

E-commerce — Print on demand

FEB 2023 - AT THE MOMENT

Traffic management, SEO, analytics, affiliate system, marketing and sales funnel.

Coferpol — Backend developer

MAY 2021 - FEB 2023

Go, DevOps, UML, bare-metal, nginx, docker, TDD, POO, Cloudflare, Postgres.

Coferpol — *T.I.* Assistant

FEB 2020 - APR 2021

User support, hardware, mikrotik, unifi.

Rosa Mística — T.I. Analist

OCT 2019 - FEB 2020

IT infrastructure analysis and management, user support.

Flash Net Brasil — Technical support

OCT 2017 - MAY 2019

Customer support, monitoring and network equipment configuration.

Silk Cromia — Art finishment

IAN 2016 - OCT 2017

Creating artwork for different types of media.

NOTES

Good communication.
Creates documentation.
Immediate start availability.

LANGUAGES

Technical english, read, write and listen - Native Portuguese.

EDUCATION

Alura

2020 - 2022

Owasp Security, Go, Linux, Docker, UI-UX, JavaScript

Unifev — Advertising and marketing

2018 - 2019

(Incomplete) Writing, scripting, creation process, artistic look.

IFSP — Analysis and systems development

2017 - 2017

(Incomplete) Statistics, basic logic, basic network.

IFSP — Computer maintenance and support

2014 - 2016

High school and integrated technical education, UML, database, logic, linux...